Guide to the Account Books Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- NUMERICAL, 1786-1925; Series III; 3.5 linear feet (9 boxes)
  - NUMERICAL, 1-21
    - No. 14: Wardwell, Claison Shaw [N.Y. dentist]: 2 account books, 1879-1886 (Box 156, Folder 12-13)
    - No. 15: Elwood, Everett S.: 2 household account books, 1870-1872 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - No. 16: [New Haven militia company?]: tally book, 1812-1818 (Box CF1)
    - No. 17: Saybrook Bank, Essex, Connecticut
      - 2 business letterbooks, 1887-1890 (Box 158, Folder 15-16)
      - 2 business letterbooks, 1901-1902, 1904 (Box 159, Folder 17-18)
    - No. 18: Unidentified daybook, 1867-1868 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - No. 19: Williams, Frederick Wareham: account book kept while a student at Sheffield Scientific School, New Haven, 1887-1888 (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - No. 20: Oviatt, Edwin: account book, 1905-1907 (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - No. 21:
  - NUMERICAL: OVERSIZE
    - No. 3: Half-Way House, Thousand Islands: 2 tavern account books, 1816-1835 (Box 162)
    - No. 21: Cooke, Increase & Company, New Haven [bookseller]: "Yale College journal", 1805-1814 (Box 162)
- Additional Material, Accession 2003-M-007
  - Ledger of unidentified local tradesman/contractor [contains some items pertaining to Yale College], 1826-1891 (Box 1)